Novak, welcome back to Cincinnati.
诺瓦克 欢迎回到辛辛那提
What were the key factors in your decision
是什么让你决定
to return?
回来打？
Thank you.
谢谢
Well, I honestly wanted
说实话 我想
to have uh at least uh you know,
至少
one tournament coming into US Open.
在美网之前打一站
Um haven't played
我从温网之后
since uh since Wimbledon
就没打过比赛
and my body reacted quite well
而温网之后
after Wimbledon.
我的身体反应相当好
It was the best that my body felt
说实话 那是过去两年里
after any Grand Slam in the last two years
任何一个大满贯之后
to be honest.
我身体最好的一次
any other grand slam I played
过去两年我打的每一个大满贯
in the last two years there was some kind
之后都会有
of injury with different severity
或轻或重的伤
that took more time for me to address
要花更多时间去处理
and then come back competing
才能回来比赛
so this time I was healthy
而这次我是健康的状态
and um I I really wanted to play I kind
我很想打
of missed it and here I am
有点想念它 所以我来了
your first time back here
这是 2023 年之后
since 2023 in a career of great matches
你第一次回到这里
where does that final against Alcaraz sit
那场决赛你排第几？
one of the top I say top three finals that I've
我会说 排前三
that I've played best of three uh sets,
在我打过的三盘制决赛里
you know, in Masters events.
大师赛这一档
No doubt.
毫无疑问
Uh just incredible, thrilling,
太不可思议了 又惊险又刺激
exciting roller coaster like
像坐过山车
the Park Next Door uh type of ride um
就是隔壁那个游乐园里的那种
of a match.
一场那样的比赛
I think it went almost four hours.
我记得打了快四个小时
Uh played on the sun,
我们在太阳底下打
we played with the shade,
又在阴影里打
we ended up almost in evening hours.
最后快打到晚上
Uh was really anybody's game.
谁赢都有可能
I had match points and then,
我拿到过赛点 然后
you know, came back
他又追了回来
and tie break uh really nerve-wracking
进了抢七 对我们俩来说
for for both of us and we gave it all.
都太熬人了 我们拼尽了全力
Um so that was the last time I actually
那是我上一次
played him in this tournament, you know,
在这站比赛跟他交手
three years ago when I won the title.
三年前 我拿了那个冠军
So exciting to to be back.
能回来真的很兴奋
We wish you a wonderful week.
祝你这一周顺利
Thank you.
谢谢